Guide to the Cannon Mills Records, 1836-1983 RL.00187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Charles Albert Cannon Series, 1836-1971, bulk 1916-1963
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Consolidation of 1928: (Box 18)
      - Stock of Charles A. Cannon, Shares Bought from Safe (Box 18)
      - Deposit and Trust Co. (Box 18)
      - Stock of Mr. and Mrs. E. T. Cannon (Box 18)
      - Stock of J. Ross Cannon (Box 18)
      - Stock of Mrs. Mary E. Cannon (Box 18)
      - Stock of Mrs. Ruth C. Cannon (Box 18)
      - Stockholders' Lists for the Nine Mills at Cease of Business, 5 P.M., 1928, June 20 (Box 18)
      - Stockholders' Original Lists for the Nine Mills at Close of Business, 1928, June 30 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence (Including Financial Papers), 1918- 1926, 1930 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence:
      - March, 1938 (Box 18)
      - March, 1938 (G. A. Batte, Secretary to C. A. Cannon) (Box 18)
      - 1946-1967 and undated (Box 18)
    - Electric Power, 1923-1926 (Box 18)
    - Employment Inquiry, 1920 (Box 18)
    - Estate of James William Cannon: Executive vs. Collector of Internal Revenue:
      - Statement of Plaintiffs, 1925 (Box 18)
      - Answer of Defendant, 1926 (Box 18)
      - Petition and Exhibit B (Box 18)
      - Complete Report Investigation of James W. Cannon, Jack E. Buckley, Special Accountant (Box 18)
      - Exhibits R and AA-DD List and Exhibit AA (Box 18)
      - Exhibits BB, CC, and DD (Box 18)
    - Estate of James William Cannon: Executors vs. Collector of Internal Revenue: (Box 19)
      - Figures for Consideration in Any Negotiations (Box 19)
      - Franklin Cotton Mills' Accounts with H. Hentz and Co., New York, 1916-1918, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Franklin Cotton Mills' Accounts with J. S. Bache and Co., New York, 1917-1918 (Box 19)
      - Information on Franklin Cotton Mills, 1916-1927, Furnished to Walter G. Mitchell, Special Accountant, 1927 (Box 19)
      - List of Correspondence and Reports (Box 19)
      - List of Records and Papers (Box 19)
      - Memoranda (Box 19)
      - Memoranda and Auditors' Report Papers Returned by Cansler and Cansler, Attorneys at Law, 1929, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Report of Walter G. Mitchell, Special Accountant, 1927 (Box 19)
      - Stock of Mrs. M. E. Cannon (Box 19)
    - Estate of Ella Lowe Smith (Box 19)
    - Estate Records of Thomas T. Smith, Jr., (Former Secretary of Cannon Manufacturing Co.), C. A. Cannon, Co-Executor: (Box 20)
      - 1917-1940 (bulk 1930s), 6 folders (Box 20)
      - Volumes (Box 20)
    - Goldman Sachs and Co., 1956 (Box 20)
    - Halifax Cotton Mills, South Boston, Va., 1923-1924 (Box 20)
    - Index to Inactive Subject Files Filed in WarehouseYear Ending Dec. 31, 1941 (Box 20)
    - Insurance:
      - Family Policies, 1943 (Box 20)
    - Jordan, Senator B. Everett: 1960, 1970-1971, (Photocopies from Jordan Papers) (Box 20)
    - Klumac Cotton Mills, Salisbury, N.C.: (Box 21)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 21)
      - 1936 (Box 21)
    - Labor Troubles at Concord, undated (1900-1920s) (Box 21)
    - Lever Brothers, 1953 (Box 21)
    - Life Magazine, 1954 (Box 21)
    - Masons: Stokes Lodge No. 32, Concord, N.C.:
      - 1918-1933 (Box 21)
      - 1934 (Box 21)
      - Repurchase Agreement with R. L. Burrage, 1934-1944 (Box 21)
    - Mecklenburg Mills Company, Salisbury, N.C.:
      - Letter, 1923, and Audit Report and Balance Sheet for 1922 (Box 21)
    - Men of Achievement, Inc., 1952 (Box 21)
    - Military Service Exemption, 1917 (Box 21)
    - Monument Mills, Inc., New York, 1954 (Box 21)
    - National Cotton Council:
      - 1953 (Box 21)
      - Projected Foreign Trade Program, 1955 (Box 21)
      - Projected Production and Marketing Program, 1955 (Box 21)
      - Projected Sales Promotion Program, 1955 (Box 21)
    - News Clippings, 1932 and undated (Box 22)
    - Niblock, F. C., Loan, 1931-1945 (Box 22)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway Company:
      - Financial Statement, 1916, July-Dec. (Box 22)
    - Odell Manufacturing Company:
      - Minutes, 1879-1899 (Typescript) (Box 22)
      - Minutes, 1899-1902, with Data, 1890-1897, on New England Mills Appended (Typescript) (Box 22)
    - Personal Files:
      - 1921, A-Y, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Pope, J. B., Loan Papers, 1927-1941 (Box 22)
    - Rates Paid Per Week to Employees by Categories, 1922, Oct.-Nov. Southern Elevator Company:
      - Elevator at Cannon Residence, 1955 (Box 22)
    - Spindle-Hours Operated at Cannon Mills, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Spindle-Hours and Loom-Hours Operated at Amazon, Central, Imperial, Social Circle, and Wiscassett Mills, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Stock Sales and Purchases, 1920 (Box 23)
    - Stock Transfers: James H. Dooley, 1924 (Box 23)
    - Stocks of Wiscassett Mills, Cannon Mills, etc., 1925-1947 (Box 23)
    - Stribling vs. Cannon Mills et al.:
      - Memorandum of Agreement between William A. Stribling, Cotton Buying and Receiving Agent at Atlanta, and M. L. Cannon, 1925, May 29 1928-1930, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Cabarrus Cotton Mills, 1925-1927, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Stribling vs. Cannon Mills, et al.: (Box 24)
      - Durham Hosiery Mills, 1925-1929 (Box 24)
      - Imperial Cotton Mills, 1926-1930, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Surplus and Depreciation, 1926 (Box 24)
    - Taxation:
      - Federal Tax Litigation, 1928 (Box 24)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations:
      - 1950 (Box 24)
      - Companies Not Responding, 1952 (Box 24)
      - Companies Not Participating, 1952 (Box 24)
      - Companies Paying Dues, 1952 (Folders 1-2) (Box 24)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations: (Box 25)
      - Companies Paying Dues, 1952 (Folders 3- 4) (Box 25)
      - Companies Possibly Participating, 1952 (Box 25)
      - Correspondence, 1951, Feb.-Nov., 5 folders (Box 25)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations: (Box 26)
      - Correspondence, 1951, Dec.-1953, Jan., 13 folders (Box 26)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations: (Box 27)
      - Financial Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 27)
      - Fall Meeting, 1952, Oct. 21 (Box 27)
      - Information, 1951, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Meetings, 1948-1950 (Box 27)
      - Meetings, 1951, March-Dec., 4 folders (Box 27)
      - Membership Lists, 1951-1953 (Box 27)
      - Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 27)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations: (Box 28)
      - Subscribers, 1951-1952 (Box 28)
      - Subscription Cards, 1951, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Subscription Letters, 1950-1951 (Box 28)
      - Subscription Letters, 1952, Feb.-June 19, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations: (Box 29)
      - Subscriptions, 1951, June 20-1951, Dec., 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Valdese, N.C., Water and Sewer Bonds, 1932 (Box 29)
    - Weaving Loom-Hours Operated, 1954 (Box 29)
    - Weekly Order Reports, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Volumes Shelved in Numerical Sequence
    - Charles Albert Cannon: Dividends (Volume 1)
      - Received, 1933-1938 (bulk, 1933-1937); Interest (Box 29)
      - Received, 1933-1938 (bulk, 1933-1937); Cash (Box 29)
      - Receipts and Disbursements, 1921, Dec.-1932, Dec. (Box 29)
    - Ledger Prepared in 1928 for Estates of James William Cannon as Security Record of Securities Investments, 1913-1920, of James William Cannon and Mary Ella Bost Cannon (Volume 2)
- Eugene Thomas Cannon Series, 1921-1948
  Primarily legal and financial papers of this son and heir of James W. Cannon and Mary Ella (Bost) Cannon including financial correspondence of Mrs. E. T. Cannon. This series contains copies of wills, court documents, and financial reports and letters from the trustees of James W. Cannon's estate, and including information relating to the estate that is not available elsewhere in the collection. Other topics include taxes, a suit against Appalachian Hall, an institution at Asheville specializing in the treatment of nervous disorders, and Davidson Cotton Mills, a Cannon family enterprise.
  - Boxed Files
    - Bank of Asheville: (Box 30)
      - Bank Statements, 1947-1948 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence of Mrs. Eugene T. Cannon, 1946-1954, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Davidson Cotton Mills:
      - Letter, 1936, and Certificate of Incorporation and Minutes of Stockholders and Directors, 1923-1938 (Box 30)
    - Estate of James William Cannon:
      - Will, 1921 (Box 30)
      - Court Documents, 1923-1941, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Financial Reports of Trustees, 1926-1945, 4 folders (Box 30)
      - Trust Accounts and Papers with City Bank Farmers Trust Company, 1938-1944 (Box 30)
    - Estate of Joseph F. Cannon: (Box 31)
      - Accounts, 1939 (Box 31)
    - Estate of Mary Ella (Bost) Cannon (Mrs. James William Cannon):
      - Will, 1923-1937 (Box 31)
      - Court Documents, 1938-1945 (Box 31)
      - Trust Papers with City Bank Farmers Trust Company, 1923-1938 (Box 31)
    - Eugene T. Cannon vs. Appalachian Hall, Inc., etc., 1942-1943, 1948 (Box 31)
    - Taxes, 1937-1944, 4 folders (Box 31)
- Martin Luther Cannon Series, 1907-1918
  Insurance agency ledger recording accounts with mills in the Cannon group, other textile mills, non-textile businesses, James W. Cannon, and T. W. Smith.
  - Information Folder (Box 31)
  - Martin Luther Cannon's Insurance Agency Ledger, 1907-1918 (Box 31)
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 32)
      - Lists of Companies (Box 32)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955:
      - Aileen Mills--The Burg Company (Box 32)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 33)
      - Wm. Caine Co.--Crystal Laundry (Box 33)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 34)
      - Dawson-Thornton Dry Goods Co.--J. Gladstone Co. (Box 34)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 35)
      - Goeke Co.--James A. Hern & Son (Box 35)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 36)
      - Hibben Hollweg & Co.--Mayer & Osterman (Box 36)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 37)
      - Miscellaneous--Oriole Dry Goods Co. (Box 37)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 38)
      - Pacific Embroidery Co.--Russell Manufacturing Co. (Box 38)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 39)
      - Schulte-United, Inc.,--Textile Mills Co. (Box 39)
    - Bankruptcy and Bad Debts, 1926-1955: (Box 40)
      - E. H. Thompson Co.--Walter L. Yost (Box 40)
    - Breckinridge, L. D., Cotton Goods Broker, St. Louis, Missouri: (Box 41)
      - 1926-1928 (Box 41)
      - 1924-1929 (Box 41)
    - Brown-Harry Co., General Contractors on Various Projects, 1926-1927 (Box 41)
    - Cannon Manufacturing Co., etc., vs. County of Cabarrus, etc, 1922 (Box 41)
    - Census of Manufactures, 1923, 1925 (Box 41)
    - Coddle Creek Pipe Line, 1926-1927 (Box 41)
    - Commission File, 1917-1922 (Box 41)
    - Computation Rules, undated (Box 41)
    - Consolidation of Cannon Manufacturing Co., Cabarrus Cotton Mills, Barringer Manufacturing Co., Franklin Cotton Mills, Gibson Manufacturing Co., Kesler Manufacturing Co., Patterson Manufacturing Co., Norcott Mills Co., and Hobarton Manufacturing Co. into Cannon Mills Company, 1928, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Consolidation of Cannon Manufacturing Co., Cabarrus Cotton Mills,..into Cannon Mills Company, 1928 (Continued, 3 folders) (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1933, June 3 (Box 42)
    - Curtin and Brockie, Fire Insurance, Philadelphia, Pa., 1931-1932 (Box 42)
    - Dividend, 1928, Oct. 1, Stock Transferred after Sept.18 (Box 42)
    - Dividends, 1928-1929 (Box 42)
    - Dividends Accrued, 1928, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Dividends on Common Stock, 1928 (Box 42)
    - Financial Statements: (Box 43)
      - 1912-1925, 3 folders (Box 43)
      - 1926-1935, 1953, 1974-1975, and undated (Box 43)
      - Composite, 1909-1918 (Box 43)
      - General Files, 1927-1929, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Financial Statements: (Box 44)
      - General Files, 1930-1933, 4 folders (Box 44)
    - Financial Statements, Inventories, and Sales Information, 1919-1935 (bulk, 1920s) (Box 44)
    - Financial Statements and Sales and Sheeting Billings, 1933-1941 (Box 44)
    - Fire Claims, 1934-1935, 4 folders (Box 45)
    - Fire Claims and Insurance, 1919-1922, 4 folders (Box 45)
    - Fire Claims and Insurance, 1923-1927, 5 folders (Box 46)
    - First Baptist Church, Kannapolis, Construction File:
      - 1922-1923, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - First Baptist Church, Kannapolis, Construction File: (Box 47)
      - 1923, June-1924, Feb. (Box 47)
      - Time Books, 1922 (Box 47)
    - Franklin Cotton Mills:
      - 1921, 1924, 1926, Jan.-May, 1927 (Box 47)
      - 1927, June-Dec. (Box 47)
      - 1928, Jan.-Feb. (Box 47)
      - 1928, March (Box 47)
      - 1928, April-Aug., 1929-1930, undated (Box 47)
    - General File, 1923 (Box 47)
    - General File, 1924-1926, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Insurance, 1919 (Box 48)
    - Inventory, Taxes, etc., 1916 (Box 48)
    - Inventory, 1918-1919, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Inventory, 1920-1925, 6 folders (Box 49)
    - Bureau of Internal Revenue's Instructions, 1922
      - Goods in Process, 1925, Dec. (Box 49)
    - Inventory: Special Cotton Inventory, 1923, July 31 Joint Accounts: (Box 50)
      - 1925 (Box 50)
      - 1926 (Box 50)
    - Kannapolis:
      - Central High School Construction and Equipment, including Louis H. Ashbury, Architect, Charlotte, N.C. (Box 50)
      - 1924-1925, 3 folders (Box 50)
      - Cashbook, 1924-1925 (Box 50)
      - Ledger, 1924-1925 (Box 50)
    - North Kannapolis Graded School Construction
      - Including Frank B. Simpson, Raleigh Architect (Box 50)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 50)
    - Kannapolis: (Box 51)
      - Public School Building Construction and Equipment, 1920-1921, 7 folders (Box 51)
      - YMCA Construction, M. E. Boyer, Jr., Architect, 1924-1928 (Folder 1) (Box 51)
    - Kannapolis: (Box 52)
      - YMCA Construction, M. E. Boyer, Jr., Architect, 1924-1928 (Folders 2-3) (Box 52)
      - YMCA Trial Balances, 1929-1938, 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Kerr Bleachery and Finishing Works, 1925-1926 (Box 52)
    - Land and Buildings Purchased, 1927-1930 (Box 52)
    - Mercantile Rents, Dec., 1936 (Box 52)
    - Mill House Insurance and Costs at Kannapolis, 1920- 1927 (Box 52)
    - Mill House Removal, 1926 (Box 52)
    - Mill House Rental Cards, 1922-1928 and undated (Box 52)
    - Mill Houses, 1929-1932 (Box 52)
    - Mill No. 3 Construction and Equipment, 1925 (Box 52)
    - Mill No. 3 Remodeling, 1926-1927 (Box 52)
    - Mill No. 6 Addition Insurance and Costs, 1925 (Box 52)
    - Mill No. 7, Kannapolis, Construction, 1925-1927 (Box 53)
    - New Machinery, 1924-1925 (Box 53)
    - Property and Building Additions, 1923-1928 (Box 53)
    - Southern Power Company, 1919-1927, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Stock:
      - Cabarrus Cotton Mills Stock Retired, 1928 (Box 53)
      - Cabarrus Cotton Mills Preferred Stock Exchanged for Cannon Mills Stock, 1928-1929 (Box 53)
    - Stock: (Box 54)
      - Cannon Manufacturing Co. Stock Deposited for Cannon Mills, 1928 (Box 54)
      - Common Stock Certificates Issued, 1928, July (Box 54)
      - Gibson Manufacturing Co. Preferred Stock, 1928 (Box 54)
      - Preferred Stock Certificates, 1928 (Box 54)
      - Preferred Stock for Redemption, 1928 (Box 54)
      - Preferred Stock Retired, 1928 (Box 54)
    - Stock Shares, Receipts, and Dividend Payments, 1928 (Box 54)
    - Stock Transfers, 1922-1925 (Box 54)
    - Stock Transfers, 1925-1928, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Stock Transfers and Dividends, 1928 (Box 55)
    - Stock Transfers, Receipts, and Dividend Payments, 1928, July (Box 55)
    - Taxes, 1912-1921, 6 folders (Box 56)
    - Taxes, 1921-1935, 7 folders (Box 57)
    - Taxes, 1936-1941, 6 folders (Box 58)
      - Brief to Commissioner of Internal Revenue, 1923, Dec. 11, Concerning Taxes for 1911-1920 (Box 58)
      - Excise, 1941 (Box 58)
      - Income, 1909-1928, 3 folders (Box 58)
      - Local Tax Receipts, 1904-1914 (Box 58)
    - Taxes: (Box 59)
      - North Carolina, 1917-1928, 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Patterson Manufacturing Co., 1927 (Box 59)
      - Property, 1917-1928, 6 folders (Box 59)
      - York, S.C., Plant's South Carolina Taxes, 1923-1928, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Trial Balances, 1926-1935, 5 folders (Box 60)
    - Warehouse J Addition, Brown-Harry Co., General Contractors, 1925-1927 (Box 60)
    - Yarn Billings, 1928 (Box 60)
- Secretaries' Office Series, 1887-1973, bulk 1920s-1930s
  Files during tenures of successive secretaries J. W. Cannon, Jr., G. B. Lewis, T. T. Smith, Jr., F. J. Haywood, Hearne Swink, J. H. Cannon, and B. T. Beck, concerning mostly the corporation's charter, stock and stockholders. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files
    - Charter and By-Laws, 1887-1888, and Letter and List of Officers, 1916 (Box 60)
    - Charter Amendment and Stock Transfer, 1922:
      - 1922 (Box 60)
      - Correspondence (Box 60)
      - Proxies for Sept. 28 (Box 60)
      - Proxies for Nov. 14, A-Y, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Charter Amendment and Stock Transfer, 1922: (Box 61)
      - Transfer Letters, A-Y, 5 folders (Box 61)
    - Correspondence:
      - 1938, March (Box 61)
    - Notices to Stockholders Enclosing Temporary Stock (Box 62)
      - Certificates of Cannon Mills Company, 1928-1934 (bulk, 1928) (Box 62)
    - Receipts from Stockholders for Temporary Stock
      - Certificates of Cannon Mills Company, 1928-1934 (bulk, 1928) (Box 62)
    - Stock Transfers, 1920s-1930s: (Box 63)
      - Estates, B-Y, 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Stockholders:
      - Notice to Bearers of Scrip Certificates for Fractional Shares, 1973 (Box 63)
      - Notices of Annual Meetings, 1923, 1961-1972 (Box 63)
- Executive Office Files Series, 1923-1980, bulk 1940s-1970s
  Files include annual reports; cloth samples; correspondence; economic stabilization; electric power meter reading cards for rental buildings and houses (includes names of workers); President Don S. Holt and his speeches; merino yarn; the retirement plan; the union election in 1974 lost by the Textile Workers Union of America (communications to and from employees included); the W. T. Grant Company; an investigation of corporate slush funds; a suit involving racial discrimination; and civic projects. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute: (Box 63)
      - Audit Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 63)
      - Committee for Good Government, 1975-1980 (Box 63)
      - Economic Research and Information Activity, 1974 (Box 63)
    - Annual Reports to the Stockholders, 1928-1975, 5 folders (Box 63)
    - Ballots, 1976 (Box 63)
    - Banks' Annual Reports, 1971 (Folder 1) (Box 63)
    - Banks' Annual Reports, 1971 (Folder 2) (Box 64)
    - Brown Manufacturing Company, Concord, N.C., 1956- 1963, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Cabarrus County Hospital
      - Boiler Plant, 1949-1951 (Box 64)
      - Preliminary Cost Estimates, 1949 (Box 64)
    - Cabarrus County United Way Campaign, 1972-1979, 4 folders (Box 64)
    - Cannon Foundation: (Box 65)
      - Building Rentals in New York City: 1953, Sept.-1954, April (Box 65)
      - Building Rentals in New York City: 1954, May-Oct. (Box 65)
    - Cannon Visitor Center, 1971-1974, 3 folders
      - Preliminary Exhibition Outline, 1972 (Box 65)
    - Castle, Thomas H. (New York Office):
      - Advertising, 1969-1970 (Box 65)
    - Cincinnati Warehouse Sales and Expenses, 1969 Cloth Samples: (Box 66)
      - 1931-1938 and undated, 5 folders (Box 66)
      - 1953 and undated: Styles G40-G55 (Box 66)
      - 1953 and undated: styles G65-G90 or G91 (Box 66)
      - 1953 and undated: styles 130-200, Travora, and Muslins (Box 66)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1960, 6 folders (Box 66)
    - Correspondence: (Box 67)
      - 1961-1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box 67)
      - All Plants, 1964, 1966 (Box 67)
      - Business, 1965-1969, 5 folders (Box 67)
      - Chronological Record, 1963 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence: (Box 68)
      - Personal, 1963-1969, 4 folders (Box 68)
    - Cotton, Inc., 1974 (Box 68)
    - Courtenay Manufacturing Company, Newry, S.C.:
      - Audit Report, 1928, Sept. 29 (Box 68)
    - Debit Memoranda for Employees, Plant No. 1, No. 11 Ledger, 1936, Jan.-Feb. (Box 68)
    - Directors' Meeting, 1974, Oct. 25 (Box 68)
    - Economic Stabilization:
      - American Textile Manufacturers Institute Economic Stabilization Committee, 1971 (Box 68)
      - American Textile Manufacturers Institute Economic Stabilization Committee Meeting, 1971, Sept. 20 (Box 68)
      - American Textile Manufacturers Institute Economic Stabilization Committee Meeting, 1972, July 25 (Box 68)
      - Cotton-Korean War, 1951 and 1971 (Box 68)
      - Price Control-Korean War Presidential Authority, 1950 and 1971 (Box 68)
      - Presidential Delegation of Authority, Textile Control, 1951 and 1971 (Box 68)
    - Electric Power Meter Reading Cards for Rental Buildings and Houses Including Names and Addresses of Renters, 1932 (Box 68)
    - Electric Power Meter Reading Cards for Rental Buildings and Houses Including Names and Addresses of Renters: (Box 69)
      - 1933-1935, 3 folders (Box 69)
      - 1942, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Electric Power Meter Reading Cards for Rental Buildings and Houses Including Names and Addresses of Renters: (Box 70)
      - 1946, 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Elon College, 1972 (Box 70)
    - Employees, 1923: Names, Employment, Affiliations, etc. (Box 70)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1975 (Box 70)
    - Fluoridation, 1976 (Box 70)
    - Harden, John, Associates, 1975 (Proposed History of Cannon Mills) (Box 70)
    - Haskins and Sells, Certified Public Accountants, Charlotte, N.C., 1959-1973 (Box 70)
    - Historical Notes on Personnel and Facilities, 1930s (Box 70)
    - Holt, Don S.:
      - Article in the Concord Tribune, 1972, April 23 (Box 70)
      - Phi Psi Man of the Year, North Carolina State University, 1973 (Box 70)
      - Retirement Letters and Notices, 1974-1975 (Box 70)
      - Speeches, 1971-1972 (Box 70)
    - Holt, Don S.: (Box 71)
      - Speeches, 1973-1974 and undated, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Holt, Margaret McConnell (Mrs. Don S. Holt), Artist:
      - Vita (Box 71)
    - Inaoka Kogyo Ltd., Japan, 1974-1979 (Box 71)
    - Internal Revenue Service Investigations of Corporate Slush Funds, 1976-1977 (Box 71)
    - Ledger Accounts Classification (Box 71)
    - Letters to Cannon People, 1975-1979 (Box 71)
    - LIFO Inventory:
      - 1975 (Box 71)
      - Social Circle Cotton Mill, 1975 (Box 71)
    - Maiden Knitting Mills, Maiden, N.C.:
      - 1969-1976 (Box 71)
      - Dressmaker Fabrics, Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 71)
    - Merino Yarn, 1943-1947, 5 folders (Box 72)
    - Merino Yarn: (Box 73)
      - 1952-1954 (Box 73)
      - Analyses, 1944-1947 (Box 73)
      - Contracts, 1944-1946 (Box 73)
      - Information, 1944-1947 (Box 73)
      - Laboratory Tests, 1951-1952, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Reports, 1944-1947 (Box 73)
      - Reports, 1951-1952, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Specifications, 1951-1953 (Box 73)
    - Natural Gas, 1975-1976 (Box 74)
    - North Carolina Citizens Association, 1974 (Box 74)
    - North Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Office of Federal Contract Compliance (Equal Opportunity in Employment), 1968 (Box 74)
    - Personnel:
      - No. 6W. Service Record, World War II, 1940-1947 (Box 74)
      - Paymaster's Record of Employees Living in Company Houses, 1939-1969 (Box 74)
    - Private Code Books, 1920s and 1930s (Box 74)
    - Production Report, Plant No. 1, Mill No. 1, 1936, Dec. 23 (Box 74)
    - Quotes, Sayings, etc. (Box 75)
    - Railroad Revitalization and Regulatory Reform Act of 1975 (H.R. 9082) (Box 75)
    - Recommendations for Looms, 1964 (Box 75)
    - Retirement Plan:
      - Account Book, 1947-1954 (Box 75)
      - Administrative Manual, 1940s (Box 75)